Rosa Parks Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- General Correspondence, 1928-2006 (Box 3-13)
  - Alphabetical file (Box 3)
    - Hooks, Benjamin and Frances, holiday greeting, undated
    - Jackson, Jesse, holiday greeting and campaign ephemera, 1987-1988 See also Oversize
    - John Paul II, Pope, letter from Parks, 1999-2005
    - King, Corretta Scott, birthday greetings, 2000-2001 For additional material see Container 15, Martin Luther King, Jr. Center for Nonviolent Social Change
    - King, Martin Luther, Jr., 1956-1957, undated
    - Mitford, Jessica ("Decca" Treuhaft), letter from Parks, 1956
    - Moore, Audley, 1957
    - Posey, Webster W., letter from Parks, 1957
    - Randolph, A. Philip, 1976
    - Rangel, Charles B., 1997
  - Chronological file
    - 1948-1949
    - 1954-1955
    - 1956-1957
    - 1958-1959
    - 1960-1968
    - 1970-1975
    - 1976-1979
    - 1980-1983
    - 1984-1985
    - 1986-1987 (Box 5)
    - 1988
    - 1989
      - 1989, Jan.-Feb.
      - 1989, Apr.-Sept.
    - 1990-1991
    - 1992
      - 1992, Jan.-Mar.
      - 1992, May-Oct.
    - 1993
    - 1994
      - 1994, Jan.-Apr.
      - 1994, May-Oct.
    - 1995 (Box 6)
    - 1996
      - 1996, Jan.-Mar.
      - 1996, Apr.-Dec.
    - 1997
      - 1997, Feb.-Apr.
      - 1997, May
      - 1997, June-Dec.
    - 1998
      - 1998, Jan.-June
      - 1998, July-Nov.
    - 1999
    - 2000 (Box 7)
    - 2001-2006
    - Undated
  - Greeting cards
    - 1981-1986
    - 1987
    - 1988
      - 1988, Mar.
      - 1988, Dec. 7-16
      - 1988, Dec. 17-30
    - 1989
    - circa 1980s (Box 8)
      - Folder 1
      - Folder 2
      - Folder 3
    - 1990
    - 1991
    - 1992
      - 1992, Jan.-July
      - 1992, Dec.
        - Folder 1
        - Folder 2 (Box 9)
        - Folder 3
    - 1993
    - 1994-1995
    - 1996
    - 1997
      - 1997, Feb.-May
      - 1997, Aug.-Sept. (Box 10)
    - 1998
    - 1999
    - circa 1990s
      - Folder 1
      - Folder 2
      - Folder 3
      - Folder 4
      - Folder 5
    - 2000 (Box 11)
      - 2000, Jan.
      - 2000, Feb.
      - 2000, May-Aug.
    - 2000, 2001-2004
    - 2005
    - circa 2000s
    - Undated
      - Folder 1
      - Folder 2
  - Letters and drawings from children (Box 12)
    - 1986
    - 1990-1993
    - 1994
    - 1995
    - 1996
      - 1996, Jan.-June
      - 1996, July-Sept.
    - 1997
    - 1998-1999 See also Oversize
    - 2000
      - 2000, Jan.
      - 2000, Feb. (Box 13)
        - Folder 1
        - Folder 2
        - Folder 3 See also Oversize
        - Folder 4
      - 2000, Mar.-May
      - 2000, June
        - Folder 1
        - Folder 2
    - 2002-2003 See also Oversize
    - 2005
    - Undated
- Subject File, 1937-2005 (Box 13-18)
  Correspondence, memoranda, invitations, notes, writings, interview transcripts, programs, flyers, name tags, newsletters, an instructional kit, an organizing manual, lists, certificates, song sheets, petitions, photographs, a collection of labor and political buttons, and other material pertaining to Parks's affiliation with various organizations and institutions, her participation in major civil rights events, and efforts to honor her.
  Arranged alphabetically by name of organization, institution, or event, by topic, or by type of material.
  - Churches (Box 13)
    - St. Matthew African Methodist Episcopal Church, Detroit, Mich.
      - 1965-1976
      - 1981-1986
      - 1987-1992 (Box 14)
      - 1993-1995
      - 1996-1998
      - 1999-2002, undated
    - Unidentified donation list, 1986
    - Various other churches
      - 1954-1985
      - 1986-1997
      - 1998-2002, undated
  - Congressional Black Caucus, directory and program, 1993
  - Congressional Gold Medal, guest list, 1999 See also Container VA 1, same heading
  - Conyers, John, congressional office
    - Constituent and other mailings, 1972-1990
    - Memoranda and correspondence, 1970-1987
  - Detroit Meals on Wheels Program, 1988-1989
  - Encampment for Citizenship, civil liberties workshop kit, 1955
  - Highlander Folk School, Monteagle, Tenn., 1958-circa 1968
  - Labor and political buttons, 1937-1947, 1980s, undated See Oversize (Box 15)
  - March on Washington for Jobs and Freedom, 1963, 1988
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Center for Nonviolent Social Change, 1971-1996
  - Mississippi Freedom Summer Project, name badge and event invitation, 1964
  - Montgomery Bus Boycott
    - Instructions to car-pool drivers and passengers, 1955-1956
    - Montgomery Fair date book, used as a notebook by Parks, 1955-1956
    - Printed matter, 1956, 1976
    - Typescripts annotated by Parks, circa 1956
      - Interviews by Aubrey Willis Williams
        - King, Martin Luther, Jr.
        - Nixon, Edgar Daniel
        - Parks, Rosa
      - Writings
        - Attributed to Aubrey Willis Williams
          - Folder 1
          - Folder 2
        - Unattributed
  - NAACP
    - 1955-1959
    - 1962-1972
    - 1984-1997
  - National Committee for the Rosa L. Parks Foundation, 1981-1982
  - National Committee for the Rosa L. Parks Shrine, 1976-1980
  - National Committee to Preserve Social Security and Medicare, petition signed by Parks, 1988
  - Order of Eastern Star, 1947, 1972, undated
  - Organizational flyers and mailings, 1960-1976, 1985-1995, undated
  - Packet relating to Lynette Williams, Cathy M. Garrett, and the Voices of Civil Rights project, 1981-2004
  - People's Party, 1971 (Box 16)
  - Police evidence property tag for a revolver, 1941
  - Prayer Pilgrimage for Freedom, 1957
  - Presidential Medal of Freedom, 1996
    - Certificate See Oversize
    - Medal See Container VA 1, Presidential Medal of Freedom
    - Photographs
    - Program
  - Raoul Wallenberg Committee of the United States, 1995
  - Rosa and Raymond Parks Institute for Self Development
    - 1988-1995
    - 1996-1997
    - 1998
      - 1998, Mar.-Apr. See also Oversize
      - 1998, May-Dec.
    - 2000-2005 (Box 17)
    - Undated
  - Rosa Parks Boulevard, Detroit, Mich., 1976
  - Rosa Parks Middle School, Olney, Md., 1995
  - Rosa Parks Scholarship Foundation, 1996, undated
  - Rosa Parks v. LaFace Records, 2004
  - Song sheets, undated
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference
    - General
      - 1965-1985
      - 1986-1998
    - Poor People's Campaign, Parks's identification card, 1968
  - Southern Poverty Law Center, 2000
  - United Community Services of Metropolitan Detroit, 1971-1972
  - Wayne State University, Detroit, Mich., 1968, undated (Box 18)
  - Wilmington Ten, 1974-1976
  - Women's Conference of Concerns, 1973
- Writings, Notes, and Statements, 1956-1998 (Box 18-19)
  Book galleys, drafts of writings, notes, notebooks, interviews, prayers, spiritual reflections, and statements by Parks.
  Arranged alphabetically by type of material.
  - Books (Box 18)
    - Dear Mrs. Parks: A Dialogue with Today's Youth, galleys, 1996
    - Quiet Strength: The Faith, the Hope, the Heart of a Woman Who Changed a Nation
      - Adaptation by Von H. Washington, 1996
      - Galleys, 1994
      - Publicity packet, 1994
    - Rosa Parks: My Story, flyer, review, and invoice, 1992-1998
  - Drafts of early writings See also Oversize
    - Accounts of her arrest and the subsequent boycott, as well as general reflections on race relations in the South, 1956-circa 1958, undated
      - Folder 1
      - Folder 2
    - Autobiographical, circa 1956, undated See also Oversize
    - Fragments on the Freedom Train, undated
  - Interviews
    - Miscellaneous, 1975, undated
    - Radcliffe College, Cambridge, Mass., Black Women Oral History Project, 1978
  - Notebooks
    - circa 1956
    - 1961-1962, 1985-1990, undated
  - Notes
    - Collaborations with Elaine Steele, 1995-1998, undated
    - General (Box 19)
      - 1956-1964, 1972-1990
      - Undated
  - Prayers and spiritual reflections, 1989-1990, undated
  - Statements
    - Nomination of Clarence Thomas, 1991
    - Tribute to John Conyers, 1979
- Events, 1951-2005 (Box 19-22)
  Event programs, flyers, tickets, and other printed matter.
  Arranged in two parts: events featuring or honoring Parks and a general file of events that she most likely attended even though her name does not appear in the programs. Each part is arranged chronologically within.
  - Featuring or honoring Parks (Box 19)
    - 1956-1959
    - 1960-1966
    - 1970-1979
    - 1980-1983
    - 1984
    - 1985-1986
    - 1987
    - 1988
    - 1989 See also Oversize
    - 1990
    - 1991-1992 (Box 20)
    - 1993
      - Folder 1
      - Folder 2 See also Oversize
    - 1994
    - 1995
    - 1996-1997
    - 1998
    - 1999
    - 2002-2005
    - Undated
  - General
    - 1951, 1957-1958
    - 1966-1969
    - 1970-1973
    - 1974-1976 (Box 21)
    - 1976-1979
    - 1980-1984
    - 1985-1987
    - 1988-1989
    - 1991-1995
    - 1996-1997
    - 1998
    - 2003-2004 (Box 22)
- Resolutions and Other Honors, 1967-2006 (Box 22)
  Resolutions, tributes, certificates, honorary degrees, and poetry honoring Parks. Arranged alphabetically in the following categories: congressional; institutions and organizations; miscellaneous; poetry; states, cities, and local communities; and wooden plaques and framed certificates.
  Items are arranged alphabetically within each category by name of organization, institution, person, or state. See Oversize
  - Resolutions, tributes, certificates, honorary degrees, and poetry honoring Parks. See Oversize (Box 22)
- Miscellany, 1934-2005 (Box 22-26)
  Financial, employment, insurance, estate, and medical records, appointment calendars, address books, biographical material, business cards, lists, keepsake portfolios, membership and other cards, telephone messages, a recipe, a questionnaire, sample stationery, and other material documenting Parks's daily life and material circumstances.
  Arranged alphabetically by type of material or topic.
  - Addresses, telephone numbers, and names (Box 22)
    - Address book no. 1, 1980s, undated
    - Address book no. 2, 1980s, undated
    - Loose notes, 1997, undated
  - Airline tickets and other travel-related ephemera, 1967-1968, 1984-1994, undated
  - Appointment calendars
    - 1989
    - 1991
    - 1997
  - Automobile records and drivers licenses
    - 1968-1988
    - 1991-1996 (Box 23)
  - Banking
    - Personal
      - Canceled checks and deposit slips
        - 1966-1969
        - 1971-1977
        - 1978-1982
        - 1983-1994
      - Check and deposit registers
        - 1957-1960, 1970-1972
        - 1973-1974
        - 1979-1982
        - 1983-1998
      - Statements and bank communications (Box 24)
        - 1956, 1964-1979
        - 1980-1997
    - Rosa and Raymond Parks Institute for Self Development, canceled checks, 1987-1989
  - Biographical and bibliographical information, circa 1965, 1987, undated
  - Business cards of
    - Others, 1993-1995, undated
    - Parks, undated
  - Christmas card sent by Parks, 1986
  - Employment
    - Applications, 1959, undated
    - Flack's, Montgomery, Ala., undated
    - Hampton Institute, Hampton, Va., 1957-1960
    - House of Representatives, 1965, 1977-1989
    - Montgomery Fair, Montgomery, Ala., 1950s
  - Estate, will, and funeral, 1978-1987, 2005, undated
  - Financial notes and calculations, 1959, 1979, 1998, undated
  - Income tax records for Raymond and Rosa Parks
    - 1943-1957
    - 1958-1965
    - 1966-1987
  - Invitation lists, 1988, 1996-1998 (Box 25)
  - Keepsake portfolio A
    - Contents
      - Drawing, undated
      - Holiday greeting cards and printed matter, 1994, undated
      - Postcard from Martin Luther King, Jr. See Container 4, King, Martin Luther, Jr.
    - Emptied portfolio, undated
  - Keepsake portfolio B
    - Contents
      - Notes and draft letters, circa 1997-1998
      - Printed matter, 1998-2003, undated
    - Emptied portfolio, undated
  - Life insurance, 1948, 1956-1968, 1977-1980
  - Medical
    - 1956-1958, 1965-1973
    - 1979-1999
    - 2004, undated
  - Membership cards and dues, 1961-1975, 1985-1996
  - Receipts
    - Cernitin American sale receipt books, 1985-1986
    - Donations, 1963-1969, 1978-1997
    - Household furnishings and appliances (Box 26)
      - Bishop-Parker Furniture Co., 1934-1935, 1947-1950
      - G. A. C. Credit Corp., 1952
    - Miscellaneous, 1957-1972
    - Money orders, 1957-1969, 1990
    - Poll tax, 1957
  - Recipe for featherlite pancakes, undated
  - Residences
    - Correspondence and related items, 1957-1960, 1982-1986
    - Rent receipts, 1959-1960, 1966-1967, 1978-1986
    - Riverfront Condominiums Project, Detroit, Mich., notice of intent to convert, 2004
  - Self-help questionnaire, circa 1994
  - Social security, 1940, 1986-1991
  - Stationery, undated
  - Telephone messages, 1974-1998, undated
  - Transportation passes, 1978, 1998
  - Voter registration card, 1962
- Printed Matter, 1947-2005 (Box 26-30)
  Magazines, newspapers, pamphlets, brochures, a book, commemorative stamps, calendars, and various printed ephemera either pertaining to or collected by Parks.
  - By topic (Box 26)
    - Civil rights, 1950s-1983
    - Detroit, Mich., 1960s
    - King, Martin Luther, Jr., 1969-1970, 1986, 1993, undated
    - Religion (Box 27)
      - Church, Forrest, Bringing God Home: A Traveler's Guide, undated
      - Miscellany, 1957-1997, undated
      - Our Daily Bread series, 1995-2005
  - Commemorative stamps sent to Parks, 1964-1984
  - Depictions of Parks
    - Calendars, 1981, 2000 See also Oversize
    - Card, 1994
  - Magazines
    - Mentioning Parks
      - 1960-1962
      - 1974-1976 (Box 28)
      - 1981-1984
      - 1994-1995
      - 1998
    - Not mentioning Parks
      - American Association of Retired Persons publications, 1997-1998
      - Crisis, 1968, 1973, 1997
      - Ebony
        - 1958, 1968-1974
        - 1977 (Box 29)
        - 1997
        - 1998
      - Freedomways, 1971-1972
      - Miscellaneous, 1963, 1977, 1998
  - Miscellaneous, 1964-1998, undated
  - Newspapers (Box 30)
    - Mentioning Parks
      - 1956-1962
      - 1971-1977 See also Oversize
      - 1980-1989
      - 1992-2005 See also Oversize
      - Undated
    - Not mentioning Parks
      - 1947
      - 1951-1959
      - 1967-1969
      - 1972-1977 See also Oversize
      - 1981-1986
      - 1995-1998 See also Oversize
      - Undated
- Books Owned by Parks, 1866-2001 (Box 30-40)
  Books owned by Parks. Some of the books are inscribed with the names of family members. Others contain inscriptions to Parks by the author or the person giving her the book.
  Arranged alphabetically by name of author or title.
  - Adkins, Bill, From Africa to Bethlehem, inscribed by the author, 1993 (Box 30)
  - African Methodist Episcopal Church hymnal, undated
  - Ali, Zulu, Black Man's Religion: Islam or Christianity?, inscribed by the author, 1997
  - Andrews, R. McCants, John Merrick: A Biographical Sketch, 1920
  - Bonner, John, A Child's History of the United States, vol. 3, part 2, 1866 (Box 31)
  - C. S. Hammond & Co., Hammond's Self-Revising Superior Atlas of the World, 1944
  - Carson, Clayborne, and Kris Shepard, editors, A Call to Conscience: The Landmark Speeches of Dr. Martin Luther King, inscribed by Coretta Scott King, 2001
  - Chopra, Deepak, Creating Affluence: Wealth Consciousness in the Field of All Possibilities, inscribed by the author, 1993
  - Daniels, Pearl Gray, Portrait of Fred D. Gray: Minister, Civil Rights Lawyer, and Alabama Representative, inscribed by the author and Fred D. Gray, 1975 See also Container 4, Gray, Fred D.
  - Duvall, Carol, Wanna Make Something Out of It? How to Turn Household "Junk" into Beautiful Handicrafts, inscribed by the author, 1972 (Box 32)
  - Eliot, George, Silas Marner, 1898, 1938
  - Emerson, Henry P., and Ida C. Bender, Modern English, book 2, 1908
  - Esler, L. A., Presidents of Our United States, 1936
  - Gandhi's Letters to a Disciple, inscribed by Olivia Pearl Stokes, 1950, 1957
  - Gideons International, The New Testament of Our Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ
    - 1957
    - 1965 (Box 33)
  - Good, Warren R., and Hope H. Chipman, Plane Geometry, 1933
  - Gray, Fred D., Bus Ride to Justice: Changing the System by the System, inscribed by the author, 1995
  - Hajj, Attallah, Ancestral Voices, 2000
  - Haley, Alex, Roots: The Saga of an American Family, inscribed by the author, 1976 (Box 34)
  - Holy Bible
    - C. H. Robinson and Co., with a register of family births, marriages, and deaths, 1900 See Oversize; See also Container 2, Copies of family register pages
    - World Syndicate Publishing Co., 1901, 1963-1968
  - Killens, John Oliver, Youngblood, inscribed by the author, 1954-1956, 1987 (Box 35)
  - Knox, N. L., Elementary Lessons in English, part 1, How to Speak and Write Correctly, 1886
  - Lamparski, Richard, Whatever Became Of... ?, inscribed by the author, 1973
  - Lawrance, Marion, How to Conduct a Sunday School; or, Twenty-eight Years a Superintendent, 1905
  - MacArthur, John, The MacArthur Study Bible, inscribed by Lois Harris, 1997 (Box 36)
  - Macoy, Robert, Adoptive Rite Ritual: A Book of Instruction in the Organization, Government and Ceremonies of Chapters of the Order of the Eastern Star
    - McCauley, Leona, copy, 1945, 1964-1967
    - Parks, Rosa, copy, 1945
  - McClure, A. K., Lincoln's Own Yarns and Stories, fragment, 1900
  - Meriwether, Louise, Daddy Was a Number Runner, inscribed by the author, 1970
  - Michigan Barber School, Modern Textbook of Barbering, 1957 (Box 37)
  - New Testament, published by the Haskins Service, undated
  - Parks, Rosa
    - Quiet Strength, author's copy, 1994, 2000
    - Rosa Parks: My Story, inscribed by Tim Rosarito, 1991-1992
  - Pigee, Vera, The Struggle of Struggles, part 1, inscribed by the author, 1975
  - Robinson, Jo Ann Gibson, The Montgomery Bus Boycott and the Women Who Started It: The Memoir of Jo Ann Gibson Robinson, 1987
  - Russell, C. T., Scenario of the Photo-Drama of Creation, 1914 (Box 38)
  - Shakespeare, William, Julius Caesar, 1898
  - Shannon, T. W., Self Knowledge and Guide to Sex Instruction, 1913
  - Smith, Sandra, Poems and Inspirational Thoughts, inscribed by the author, 1985
  - Sweeney, W. Allison, History of the American Negro in the Great War, 1919 (Box 39)
  - Terkel, Studs
    - Division Street: America, inscribed by the author, 1973
    - Hard Times: An Oral History of the Great Depression, inscribed by the author, 1972
  - Williamson, Marianne, The Healing of America, inscribed by the author, 1997 (Box 40)
  - Yette, Samuel F., The Choice: The Issue of Black Survival in America, 1971
- Medals, 1996-1999 (Box VA1)
  The Congressional Gold Medal and Presidential Medal of Freedom.
  Arranged alphabetically by name of the medal.
  - Medals (Box VA 1)
    - Congressional Gold Medal, 1999 See also Container 14, same heading
    - Presidential Medal of Freedom, 1996 See also Container 16, same heading
- Oversize, 1900-2006 (Box OV 1 -OV 17)
  Oversize material consisting of resolutions, tributes, certificates, honorary degrees, correspondence, writings, political ephemera, labor and campaign buttons, a calendar, a family Bible, and newspapers.
  Arranged and described according to the series, containers, and folders from which the items were removed.
  - Family Papers (Box OV 1)
    - Letters to and from Rosa Parks
      - Extended family
        - Undated (Container 1)
    - Other family papers
      - McCauley, Leona (mother)
        - Miscellany, 1980 (Container 2)
  - General Correspondence
    - Alphabetical file
      - Jackson, Jesse, holiday greeting and campaign ephemera, 1987 (Container 4)
    - Letters and drawings from children (Containers 12-13)
      - 1998-2000
      - 2003
  - Subject File (Box OV 2)
    - Labor and political buttons, 1937-1947, 1980s, undated (Container 15)
    - Presidential Medal of Freedom, 1996 (Box OV 3)
      - Certificate (Container 16)
      - Case for certificate (Container 16)
    - Rosa and Raymond Parks Institute for Self Development, 1998 (Container 16)
  - Writings, Notes, and Statements
    - Drafts of early writings
      - Autobiographical, undated (Container 18)
  - Events (Box OV 4)
    - Featuring or honoring Parks
      - 1989 (Container 19)
      - 1993 (Container 20) (Box OV 5)
  - Resolutions and Other Honors (Container 22) (Box OV 6)
    - Congressional
      - Bilbray, James H., 1989
      - Ford, Harold, 1988
      - Lautenberg, Frank, 1990
      - Mineta, Norman Y., 1993
      - Reid, Harry, 1989
      - Stokes, Louis, 1977, 1996
    - Institutions and organizations
      - African American Roundtable of Santa Clara County, Calif., 1993
      - Alpha Kappa Alpha Sorority, Eta Rho Omega Chapter, San Jose, Calif., 1993
      - Association of Teacher Educators, 1995
      - Bryant College, Smithfield, R.I., 1995
      - Congress of Racial Equality of California, undated
      - Cuyahoga Community College, Cleveland, Ohio, 1977
      - Edward Waters College, Jacksonville, Fla., 1994
      - Hebrew Union College, Jewish Institute of Religion, New York, N.Y., 1987 (Box OV 7)
      - Langston University, Langston, Okla., 1998
      - Lincoln University, Lincoln University, Pa., 1992
      - Massachusetts Civil Liberties Union Foundation, 1987
      - Morehouse College, Atlanta, Ga., 2002
      - Mount Saint Vincent University, Halifax, Nova Scotia, Canada, 1998
      - NAACP, Monroe County, Mich., branch, 1995
      - National Political Congress of Black Women, Metropolitan Montgomery Chapter, undated
      - National Urban League, 2004
      - Project Love: Remember the Children Foundation, 1997-2000
      - St. Matthew African Methodist Episcopal Church, Detroit, Mich., 1999 (Box OV 8)
      - Soka Women's Junior College, Tokyo, Japan, 1993
      - Tuskegee University, Tuskegee, Ala., 1988
      - United Committee on Negro History, 1967
      - University of Michigan, Dearborn, Mich, 1991
      - Veterans Medical Center, Tuskegee, Ala., 1988
    - Miscellaneous (Box OV 9)
      - American embassy, Nassau, Bahamas, 1996
      - City council, Toronto, Canada, 1999
      - Collins and Wolff families, 1997
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration
        - 1994
        - 1996
      - Smith, Carolyn and Kim, 2001
      - Social workers and welfare professionals, undated
    - Poetry
      - Forte, Roland A., 1973
      - Foster, Connie I. and Michael R., 1997
      - Greene-Washington, Dauress, 2001
      - Jones, Nikka S., undated
      - Kerrin, Mark T., 1996
      - Thornton, Samuel Ray, 1998
    - States, cities, and local communities
      - Alabama and Alaska, 1985, 1995-1996
      - California
        - 1985-1992
        - 1993-1994 (Box OV 10)
        - 1995
        - 1997-1999, undated
      - District of Columbia and Georgia, 1988-1999
      - Illinois, Indiana, Louisiana, Maryland, and Massachusetts, 1988-1998 (Box OV 11)
      - Michigan
        - Detroit, 1988-2004
        - General (Box OV 12)
          - 1976, 1986-1994
          - 1995-2006
      - Nevada and New Jersey, 1989-1990, 1999
      - New York, 1989-1995 (Box OV 13)
      - Ohio, 1972-1973, 1989, 1996
      - Pennsylvania and Rhode Island, 1987, 1995-1996
      - Texas, Virginia, and Washington, 1987-1996
    - Wooden plaques and framed certificates
      - California
        - Federal Prison Camp, Boron, Calif.
        - North Richmond Community, 1993 (Box OV 14)
      - Indiana, 1989
      - Michigan, 2001
      - Nevada, 1989
      - Pennsylvania, 1994
  - Printed Matter (Box OV 15)
    - Depictions of Parks
      - Calendars, 2000 (Container 27)
    - Newspapers
      - Mentioning Parks, 1975-1977, 2005 (Container 30)
      - Not mentioning Parks (Container 30)
        - 1976
        - 1977 (Box OV 16)
          - 1977, Jan.-June
          - 1977, July-Aug.
        - 1997
  - Books Owned by Parks (Box OV 17)
    - Holy Bible